Finding Aid for Housing Division (University of Michigan) Records
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Central Topical Files 1920-1978
  - 1958-1995
    - South Quadrangle (cont.) (Box 45)
      - Resident Advisor Biographies circa 1984 (cont.)
        - Slywka-Thomas (Box 45)
        - Vallay-Young (Box 45)
    - Special Programs 1972-1992 (Box 45)
    - Special Programs Director 1972-1984 (Box 45)
    - Stearns Building 1982-1993 (Box 45)
    - Student Account System 1991 (Box 45)
    - Student Activities Building 1991 (Box 45)
    - Student Data Systems 1981-1983 (Box 45)
    - Student Rights and Responsibility Code 1992-1993 (Box 45)
    - Substance Free Housing 1986-1993 (Box 45)
    - Suggestion Plan 1978-1992 (Box 45)
    - Summer Discovery 1991-1993 (Box 45)
    - Summer Sports Camp 1990-1991 (Box 45)
    - Total Quality Management 1991-1992 (Box 45)
    - Transfer Student Placement 1992 (Box 45)
    - Transition Teams 1979-1991 (Box 45)
    - Transportation 1980-1992 (Box 45)
    - Trotter House 1971-1992 (Box 45)
    - Twenty-First Century Program Report 1993 (Box 45)
    - Utilities and Energy Management Report 1986 (Box 45)
    - Visiting Student Groups 1986-1989 (Box 45)
    - WCBN Radio 1991 (Box 45)
    - Wellness Program 1988-1992 (Box 45)
    - Woodshop, Student Activities Building 1991 (Box 45)
- Greek Housing 1971-1989
  - 1971-1989
    The Greek Housing series is comprised of individual fraternity and sorority house files for the years 1971-1989 (bulk years are 1974-1988). The files vary in depth and breadth, but most contain Off-Campus Housing registration forms, chapter surveys, and inspection reports. Other documents that the researcher might find useful within the files include: member lists, violation letters, house rules, rental agreements, and colony (pre-chapter status) evaluation forms. The chapter surveys indicate the name of the president and steward, capacity of the house, number of pledges, and the alumni advisor. The registration forms contain the address of the house, president, numbers and size of sleeping rooms, in addition to the rental rate for the rooms. The inspection reports include information documenting the physical structure of the house. The reports will note previous or upcoming renovations, existing features and general code infractions.
    - Acacia 1980-1988 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Chi Omega 1976-1983 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Chi Sigma 1975-1989 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Delta Phi 1974-1989 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi 1974-1988 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Epsilon Phi 1974-1989 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Gamma Delta 1974-1987 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Kappa Lambda 1984-1988 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Omicron Pi 1979-1987 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Phi 1974-1979 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha 1988 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Phi Delta 1981-1982 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Sigma Phi 1973-1989 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Tau Omega 1971-1988 (Box 10)
    - Alpha Xi Delta 1974-1988 (Box 10)
    - Beta Theta Pi 1974-1988 (Box 10)
    - Chi Omega 1974-1979 (Box 10)
    - Chi Phi 1974-1989 (Box 10)
    - Chi Psi 1974-1989 (Box 10)
    - Collegiate Sorosis 1981-1989 (Chi Sigma) (Box 10)
    - Delta Chi 1973-1989 (Box 10)
    - Delta Delta Delta 1974-1978 (Box 10)
    - Delta Gamma 1974-1979 (Box 10)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon 1978-1987 (Box 10)
    - Delta Phi Epsilon 1986 (Box 10)
    - Delta Sigma Theta 1974 (Box 10)
    - Delta Sigma Phi 1973-1989 (Box 10)
    - Delta Tau Delta 1974-1988 (Box 10)
    - Delta Upsilon 1974-1989 (Box 10)
    - Gamma Alpha 1983 (Box 10)
    - Gamma Phi Beta 1974-1979 (Box 10)
    - Kappa Alpha Psi 1974, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Kappa Alpha Theta 1974-1979 (Box 10)
    - Kappa Delta Rho 1985-1986 (Box 11)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma 1974-1984 (Box 11)
    - Kappa Sigma 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Lambda Chi Alpha 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Omega Psi Phi 1974 (Box 11)
    - Phi Beta Sigma 1983 (Box 11)
    - Phi Delta Phi 1976-1985 (Box 11)
    - Phi Delta Theta 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Phi Gamma Delta 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Phi Kappa Psi 1983-1988 (Box 11)
    - Phi Kappa Tau 1982-1989 (Box 11)
    - Phi Sigma Kappa 1974-1986 (Box 11)
    - Phi Rho Sigma 1974-1983 (Box 11)
    - Pi Beta Phi 1974-1978 (Box 11)
    - Pi Kappa Phi 1986 (Box 11)
    - Pi Lambda Phi 1978-1988 (Box 11)
    - Psi Upsilon 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Alpha Epsilon 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Alpha Mu 1978-1989 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Chi 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Delta Tau 1973-1979 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Kappa 1984-1987 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Nu 1973-1989 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Phi 1975-1988 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Sigma Pi 1984 (Box 11)
    - Tau Epsilon Phi 1989 (Box 11)
    - Tau Gamma Nu/Trigon 1974-1987 (Box 11)
    - Tau Kappa Epsilon 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Theta Chi 1974-1987 (Box 11)
    - Theta Delta Chi 1974-1989 (Box 11)
    - Theta Xi 1974-1985 (Box 11)
    - Triangle 1976-1989 (Box 11)
    - Zeta Beta Tau 1977-1988 (Box 11)
    - Zeta Phi Beta 1974 (Box 11)
    - Zeta Psi 1975-1989 (Box 11)
    - Zeta Tau Alpha 1974-1978 (Box 11)
  - 1947-1982
    The Greek Housing, 1947-1982 subseries (1.6 linear feet) is one alphabetical listing of all of the Greek houses associated with the university; fraternities and sororities have not been separated from one another. This series spans the years 1947-1982, the bulk of the materials cover the 1960s and 1970s. The files are comprised primarily of surveys which include the name of the officers, members, and house size.
    - Alpha Chi Omega 1958-1972 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Delta Pi 1963-1972 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Epsilon Phi 1964-1972 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Epsilon Pi 1968-1970 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Gamma Delta 1963-1970 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha 1963-1969 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Omicron Pi 1963-1976 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Phi 1964-1972 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha 1969/70 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Rho Chi 1967-1968 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Sigma Phi 1966-1980 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Tau Omega 1966-1981 (Box 22)
    - Alpha Xi Delta 1965-1971 (Box 22)
    - Beta Theta Pi 1966-1981 (Box 22)
    - Chi Omega 1956-1972 (Box 22)
    - Chi Phi 1967-1976 (Box 22)
    - Chi Psi 1966-1971 (Box 22)
    - Collegiate Sorosis 1949-1972 (Box 22)
    - Delta Chi 1966-1981 (Box 22)
    - Delta Delta Delta 1953-1972 (Box 22)
    - Delta Gamma 1954-1972 (Box 22)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon 1967-1979 (Box 22)
    - Delta Phi Epsilon 1956-1970 (Box 22)
    - Delta Sigma Delta 1965-1975 (Box 22)
    - Delta Sigma Phi 1967-1970 (Box 22)
    - Delta Sigma Pi 1968/69 (Box 22)
    - Delta Sigma Theta 1963-1968 (Box 22)
    - Delta Tau Delta 1967-1971 (Box 22)
    - Delta Theta Phi 1966-1970 (Box 22)
    - Delta Upsilon 1968-1969 (Box 22)
    - Evans Scholars 1956-1968 (Box 22)
    - Gamma Phi Beta 1954-1970 (Box 22)
    - Kappa Alpha Psi 1967-1969 (Box 22)
    - Kappa Alpha Theta 1956-1972 (Box 22)
    - Kappa Delta 1955-1968 (Box 22)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma 1959-1972 (Box 22)
    - Kappa Sigma 1966-1970 (Box 22)
    - Lambda Chi Alpha 1967-1970 (Box 22)
    - Nu Sigma Nu 1966-1979 (Box 22)
    - Omega Psi Phi 1947-1958 (Box 22)
    - Phi Alpha Kappa 1967-1970 (Box 22)
    - Phi Chi 1958-1970 (Box 22)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon 1967 (Box 23)
    - Phi Delta Phi 1966-1970 (Box 23)
    - Phi Delta Theta 1966-1981 (Box 23)
    - Phi Epsilon Pi 1967-1969 (Box 23)
    - Phi Gamma Delta 1967-1980 (Box 23)
    - Phi Kappa Psi 1966-1977 (Box 23)
    - Phi Kappa Tau 1960-1979 (Box 23)
    - Phi Rho Sigma 1967-1982 (Box 23)
    - Phi Sigma Delta 1966-1970 (Box 23)
    - Phi Sigma Kappa 1967-1975 (Box 23)
    - Phi Sigma Sigma 1956-1958 (Box 23)
    - Pi Beta Phi 1956-1972 (Box 23)
    - Pi Kappa Alpha 1967-1977 (Box 23)
    - Pi Kappa Phi 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - Pi Lambda Phi 1966-1970 (Box 23)
    - Psi Upsilon 1967-1981 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Alpha Epsilon 1965-1978 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Chi 1964-1978 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Delta Tau 1953-1972 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Kappa 1961-1971 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Nu 1966-1971 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Phi 1967-1971 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1967-1976 (Box 23)
    - Sigma Pi 1966-1982 (Box 23)
    - Tau Delta Phi 1966-1967 (Box 23)
    - Tau Epsilon Phi 1961-1971 (Box 23)
    - Tau Kappa Epsilon 1960-1969, 1980 (Box 23)
    - Theta Chi 1966-1971 (Box 23)
    - Theta Delta Chi 1966-1971 (Box 23)
    - Theta Xi 1967-1981 (Box 23)
    - Triangle 1966-1981 (Box 23)
    - Trigon 1966-1981 (Box 23)
    - Zeta Beta Tau 1960-1977 (Box 23)
    - Zeta Psi 1967-1976 (Box 23)
    - Zeta Tau Alpha 1950-1970 (Box 23)
- Small Group Housing
  The Small Group Housing series (2.75 linear feet) is divided into two sub-series: Cooperative Housing, and Miscellaneous Housing. The Cooperative Housing sub-series contains files on cooperatives for the mid to late 1970s. The files are similar to those for Greek housing in that they contain small group housing questionnaires and housing inspection reports.
  - Cooperative Housing 1972-1983
    - 1972-1983
      - Binns 1978-1981 (Box 11)
      - Friends' Center 1975-1983 (Box 11)
      - Hebrew House 1974-1978 (Box 11)
      - Inter Cooperative Council 1976-1979 (Box 11)
      - Kul Hur 1978-1980 (Box 11)
      - Muslim House 1974-1980 (Box 11)
      - Sidda Loka 1976-1981 (Box 11)
      - Xanadu 1972 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Housing
    - Asher House 1980 (Box 11)
- Residence Halls 1940-1989
  The Residence Halls series (4 linear feet) spans the years 1940-1989. The series is arranged in alphabetical order, by the first name of the building (i.e. Adelia Cheever is listed under "a") in order to maintain the original order of the filing system. The term "SEE" is used to let the researcher know that the materials are located under a different heading while "See Also" indicates an additional place to look for information. The files of the Pilot program are located within the files of the Alice Lloyd dormitory and the files of the Residential College are located within the East Quad files.
  The series provides a good source for what day-to-day life was like in the dorm. Monthly reports are a good source for locating events that took place as well as policies that were instituted or changed. The files of most living units contain information on the individual that the house or dorm was named after.
  The researcher interested in a specific dorm should also look at the UM Housing Division printed collection, as the dorm booklets are very rich in information on dormitory history, policies, and opportunities.
  - 1940-1989
    - Adelia Cheever (Box 17)
      (SEE-Oxford Housing)
    - Vera Baits
      (See Also-Cedar Bend)
      - General 1967-1977 (Box 17)
      - Monthly Reports 1967-1980 (Box 17)
      - Rent Strike 1969-1970 (Box 17)
      - Resident Staff Committee 1972-1973 (Box 17)
    - Betsey Barbour
      - General
        - 1942-1944 (annual reports) (Box 17)
        - 1972-1985 (includes Newberry Hall) (Box 17)
    - Bursley Hall
      - General 1965-1983, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Monthly Reports 1966-1981 (Box 17)
      - Staff Training Program 1967-1969 (Box 17)
    - Cedar Bend
      - Planning Committee 1965-1966 (Box 17)
      - Renamed Baits 1966 (Box 17)
    - Martha Cook 1968-1976 (Box 17)
    - Couzens Hall
      (See Also Alice Lloyd)
      - General 1969-1981, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Monthly Reports 1969-1981, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - East Quad
      - General 1967-1987 (Box 18)
      - Annual Reports
        - 1948-1951 (Tyler House) (Box 18)
        - 1946/47-1947/48 (Hinsdale House) (Box 18)
      - Monthly Reports 1965-1981 (Box 18)
      - Residential College 1966-1977, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Emmanuel (French House) (Box 18)
    - Fletcher Hall
      - General 1968-1975 (annual reports) (Box 18)
      - Annual Reports 1942/43, 1944/45 (Box 18)
    - Henderson House 1940-1977 (Box 18)
    - Language Houses (Box 18)
    - Lawyers Club
      - General 1969-1982 (Box 18)
      - Board of Governor's Meetings 1968-1986 (Box 18)
      - Medieval and Renaissance House 1972-1977 (Box 18)
      - Monthly Reports 1969-1981 (Box 18)
      - Rate Committee 1975-1983 (Box 18)
    - League Houses 1942-1943 (annual reports) (Box 18)
    - Alice Lloyd Hall
      - General 1966-1979 (Box 19)
      - Couzens Connection 1970-1972 (Box 19)
    - Alice Lloyd Hall (cont.)
      - Monthly Reports 1967-1980 (Box 19)
      - Pilot Program 1970-1986, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Pilot II 1983-1984 (Box 19)
      - Pilot Program Review Committee 1972-1973 (Box 19)
      - Student Government 1969-1971 (Box 19)
    - Mary Markley Hall
      - General 1962-1987, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Monthly Reports 1967-1981, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Max Kade German House (Box 19)
    - Mosher Jordan
      - General 1967-1980 (Box 19)
      - Coed Proposal 1969-1970 (Box 19)
      - Monthly Reports
        - 1942/43-1944/45 (Box 19)
        - 1967-1980, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Helen Newberry
      (See Also Betsey Barbour)
      - Annual Reports 1942/43-1944/45 (Box 20)
      - Monthly Reports 1966-1986 (Box 20)
    - Oxford Housing
      - General 1963-1989, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Monthly Reports 1967-1981, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Adelia Cheever
        - General 1964-1972 (Box 20)
        - Annual Reports 1942/43-1944/45 (Box 20)
      - Emmanuel (French House) 1967-1982 (Box 20)
      - Language Houses 1964-1974 (Box 20)
      - Max Kade German House 1966-1977 (Box 20)
      - Russian House 1970-1976 (Box 20)
      - Sorority Occupancy 1967-1969 (Box 20)
    - Residential College (Box 20)
      (SEE-East Quad)
    - Russian House (Box 20)
    - South Quad
      - General 1966-1987, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Monthly Reports 1966-1981, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Stockwell Hall
      - General 1966-1987 (Box 20)
      - Annual Reports 1942/43-1944/45 (Box 20)
      - Monthly Reports 1969-1981 (Box 20)
    - West Quad
      - General 1966-1988, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Annual Reports 1942/43-1944/45 (Box 21)
      - Glee Club 1942-1953 (Box 21)
      - Intramural Athletics 1945-1953 (annual reports) (Box 21)
      - Monthly Reports 1965-1980, 2 folders (Box 21)
- Family Housing 1967-1989
  The Family Housing (.9 linear feet) is arranged in alphabetical order and spans the years 1967-1989. Included in the series are monthly reports, documentation of the needs for a community center, as well as the needs of family life on the north campus.
  - 1967-1989
    - General 1971-1983, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Advisory Board Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 21)
    - Community Center 1967-1988, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Monthly Reports 1971-1980 (scattered dates) (Box 21)
    - Northwood IV
      - Planning Group 1977 (Box 21)
      - Recreation 1968-1969 (Box 21)
    - Northwood V 1968-1989, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Rate Study Committee 1969-1987 (Box 22)
    - Reports
      - Demographic and Lifestyle Research Report, undated (Box 22)
      - Family Housing Community Center Survey, 1980 (Box 22)
      - North Campus Community Center: Task Force Proposal 1981 (Box 22)
    - Task Force on Assignments and Rental Problems
      - General 1974-1975 (Box 22)
      - Final Report 1974 (Box 22)
    - University Terrace 1979-1989 (Box 22)
- Financial Records 1930-1969
  The Financial Records series (7 linear feet) includes operating statements and budgets for university housing units. The operating statements of university apartment facilities covers 1961/62 through 1968/69, while those for Mosher-Jordan Hall cover the years 1930/31 through 1932/33. Operating statements for the University Residence Halls span the years 1933/34 through 1968/69. The residence halls budgets cover the academic years 1943/44 through 1968/69.
  - Operating Statements of University Apartment Facilities (Box 25)
    - 1961/62-1968/69, 8 volumes (Box 25)
    - June Statements 1962-1969 (Box 25)
  - Operating Statements of Mosher-Jordan Halls
    - 1930/31-1932/33, 3 volumes (Box 25)
  - Operating Statements of University Residence Halls
    - 1933/34-1945/46, 13 volumes (Box 26)
    - 1946/47-1954/55, 9 volumes (Box 27)
    - 1955/56-1963/64, 9 volumes (Box 28)
    - 1964/65-1968/69, 5 volumes (Box 29)
    - June Statements 1960-1969 (Box 29)
  - Residence Hall Budgets
    - 1943/44-1959/60, 17 volumes (Box 30)
  - 1960/61-1968/69, 10 volumes (Box 31)
- Bound Minutes/Reports 1939-1977
  The Bound Minutes/Reports series (4 linear feet) contains the Board of Governors of Residence Halls minutes (1942/43 - 1969/70), Staff Meeting minutes (1966-1970), Student Advisory Committee on Housing minutes (1968-1970), University Housing Policy Board minutes (1970-1977), and the Report of the Director of Residence Halls to the Board of Governors of Residence Halls (1939/40-1941/42).
  - Board of Governors of Residence Halls, Minutes
    The minutes of the Board of Governors of Residence Halls include all exhibit handouts, however only the early years contain agendas. The minutes cover a wide variety of policies and issues regarding residential housing. There is information about new application forms, calling hours, and the Subcommittee on Evaluation of Men's Residence Halls. Issues include whether or not freshmen and upperclassmen should live together and visiting hours.
    - 1939-1941/42, 4 volumes (Box 31)
    - 1942/43-1954-1958, 13 volumes (Box 32)
    - 1958-1962-1969/70, 5 volumes (Box 33)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes 1966-1970, 2 volumes (Box 33)
    The minutes of the Staff Meetings include discussion of policies and procedures as they affect students on a day-to-day basis. Topics discussed include security and emergency procedures, visitors of opposite sex, civil infractions, damages, panty raids, and application for housing procedures. The first volume contains a listing of all meetings in the series.
  - Student Advisory Committee 1965-1970 (Box 33)
    The Student Advisory Committee on Housing, was a committee of nine students appointed by Vice President for Student Affairs, Richard Cutler. The committee was to be consulted concerning University plans for construction of student housing. Topics discussed also include vehicles on campus, small group housing, and rent strikes.
  - University Housing Policy Board
    The minutes of the University Housing Policy Board take the broadest look at housing of the university community. Meetings include documentation from the Rate Study Committee, Planning Committee, Additional Student Housing, University Housing Council, and the Family Task Information Committee. There is also discussion on rate increases: why they are needed and how to keep them as minimal as possible. There is also documentation on a possible University Credit Union (UCU) housing project, meal rebates, funding for minority lounges, meal changes, leases and eviction policies, lettuce boycotts, and the need for recreational/intramural development on campus.
    - November 1970-June 1972, 9 volumes (Box 34)
    - June 1972-March 1977, 6 volumes (Box 35)
  - Report of the Director of Residence Hall to the Board of Governors of Residence Halls 1939/40-1941/42, 3 volumes (Box 35)
    Each monthly report of the Report of the Director of Residence Halls to the Board of Governors of Residence Halls starts with a listing of the "chief actions" performed by the Board of Governors for that particular year, followed by administrative and scholarship information. Administrative information includes staff lists, residence halls/fraternity/sorority problems, and physical equipment and needs of residences. The scholarship information, which includes grade point averages of professional fraternities, dorms and league houses, is in the form of charts and textual analysis.
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs 1948-1980
    The Photographs, (0.3 linear ft.) which are arranged in alphabetical order by topic, document the Greek Houses of the university community in the late 1970s and student life of the 1980s. There are also group photographs of the residents from the Mary Markley dormitory in the 1950s. Negatives exist for many of the Greek houses and student life photographs.
    - Aerial View of Campus circa 1975, 1 photographs b&w (Box 36)
    - Bicycles on Campus 1970 (b&w) (Box 36)
    - Family Community Center 1991 (color, interior and exterior) (Box 36)
    - Greek Housing circa 1970s (b&w photos of individual houses) (Box 36)
    - Mary Markley
      - Fisher House 1958/59-1960/61 (Box 36)
        (b&w group photos)
      - Tyler House 1953/54-1957/58 (Box 36)
      - Northwood IV
        - Recreation Areas circa 1968 (Box 36)
          (color photos)
        - Walkways circa 1970 (Box 36)
          (color slides)
      - Reeves House 1977 (vandalism, color) (Box 36)
      - Students/Student Life circa 1980 (Box 36)
        (b&w and color photos-mainly Greek life, negatives included)
      - West Quad Men's Glee Club circa 1948 (Box 36)
    - South Quadrangle
      - Identified Photographs circa 1984 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous Photographs 1985-1992 (Box 45)
      - Photo Album, Bound 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Videos 1986-1993
    The Videos are arranged in chronological order and are primarily Residence Hall Repertory Theater Productions. The presentations include two or three short skits that deal with issues such as date rape, racial discrimination, and stereotypes Most productions incorporate audience participation. For a good introduction to the purpose and format of the presentations, the researcher should view the April 1990 "Talk to Us" video, as it is a promotional video for the series.
    - Residence Hall Repertory Theater Presentations (Box 37)
      - Untitled undated (re: stereotypes), VHS (Box 37)
      - "Masks," undated (re: sex roles and stereotyping) and "Welcome to Conditioning" (re: racism and discrimination), VHS (Box 37)
      - "Masks" Undated (re: sex roles and stereotyping) and "Welcome to Conditioning," undated (re: racism and discrimination) (different year) (Box 37)
        (VHS)
      - "Who's Values are You?" April 1987 (re: sexuality), VHS (Box 37)
      - "Success?" and "I Know You are, But What Am I?", VHS (Box 37)
    - Residence Hall Repertory Theater Presentations
      - "On Your Mark, Get Set, Go! But Where?" 1988/89, U-matic (Box 37)
      - "Talk to Us" January 1990 (residence hall training), VHS (Box 37)
      - "Why is the Bedroom so Crowded?" Winter 1990, VHS (Box 37)
      - "Talk to Us" April 1990 (description of the series, VHS (Box 37)
      - "Image and Identity" Winter 1991, VHS (Box 37)
      - 1991/92 Residence Halls Repertory Theater Show, VHS (Box 37)
      - "Talk to Us" Winter 1992, VHS (Box 37)
      - "Self Portraits" (re: identity and secrets) and "Say What?" (re: communication skills) April 7, 1993, VHS (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous Videos
      - "Cocaine Abuse" a talk by Steve Krapp Undated, VHS (Box 37)
      - Kelsey Video production 1986 (skits with uncomfortable social situations by students of South Quad), VHS (Box 37)
- Scrapbooks [Bimu/B6]
  The Scrapbook series contains one scrapbook that is comprised of newspaper clippings that relate to university residence hall life from 1939 to 1949. The scrapbook appears to have been created by the Housing Office.
  - Newspaper clippings 1939-1949 (Volume 1)
    (re: history of residence halls)
- Microfilm
  The Microfilm series (2 reels) was filmed by the Housing Division. The first reel probably has the most general appeal, as it is comprised of newspaper clippings from 1979-1990 that relate to Housing. The second reel contains surveys, monthly reports, residence hall library reports, and the 1976 Housing procedures manual. (Negative use copies only) [Bimu/B6/micro]
  - Housing related newspaper clippings 1979-1990 (Reel 1)
  - Big 10 Statistical Surveys 1988/89-1970/71, 1968/69-1967/68, 1965/66 (Reel 2)
  - Big 10 Facility Operation Statistics 1953-1966 (Reel 2)
  - Housing Monthly Reports to the Vice President for Student Affairs
    - December-July 1988 (Reel 2)
    - December-January 1986 (Reel 2)